Let Me Make You a Martyr is a action, mystery,
drama film directed by Corey Asraf.
A cerebral revenge film about two adopted siblings who fall in
love, and hatch a plan to kill their abusive father.
Pope, played by Marilyn Manson.
Drew Glass, played by Niko Nicotera.
June Glass, played by Sam Quartin.
Larry Glass, played by Mark Boone Junior.
Charon, played by Michael Potts.
Libby, played by Rebekah Kennedy.
Let Me Make You a Martyr is a 2016 American action crime drama film written, directed and co-produced by Corey Asraf and John Swab,
and starring Marilyn Manson, Mark Boone Junior, Niko Nicotera, Michael Potts, Sam Quartin, Slaine and Danny Boy.
The tone is intense and emotional and thought_provoking.